# Janis Rozenbergs JUNIOR FULL STACK SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

Email: janisrozkalejs@gmail.com
Mobile: +35383420133
LinkedIn - GitHub
Location: Ireland

## **PERSONAL PROFILE**

Software Developer in the process of completing a Diploma in Full Stack Software Development from the Code Institute. Currently working as a Customer Service Representative at Capita, providing exceptional customer experiences and adeptly resolving issues. I am a Sports Management & Coaching Graduate with a proven track record of over 6 years in successfully cultivating a martial arts academy, ranging from inception to establishment. With a proactive mindset, a genuine enthusiasm for learning, and a resolute commitment to professional growth, I am a valuable team player that is eager to gain entry into the tech industry.

## **KEY SKILLS**

• **Languages:** HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Python.

• Version Control: Heroku, GitHub, Git

## **EDUCATION AND TRAINING**

**Nov 2022 - Present** Customer Service Representative at Capita

**July 2016 - Oct 2022** General manager at Satori BJJ

**Sept 2016- june 2019** B.A. Sports Management & Coaching 2.1

June 2016 Leaving Certificate from Luttrellstown Community College

grades upon request

#### **PORTFOLIO PROJECTS**

Sweet Croí - Local sweet bakery website GitHub - <a href="https://github.com">https://github.com</a>
 Technologies Used - HTML , CSS

2. Rock Paper Scissors - Rock, Paper, Scissors game. GitHub - <a href="https://github.com">https://github.com</a>

Technologies Used - HTML , CSS, JavaScript

3. Fit Check - Fitness Calaculator GitHub - https://github.com

**Technologies Used** - Python, Heroku

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# Nov 2022 - Present

Customer Service Representative at Capita

All Reception duties- managing calendars & bookings

- Construction & Maintenance of <a href="www.satoribij.com">www.satoribij.com</a>
- Marketing of Satori BJJ, Lead generation
- Teaching & planning classes. A skill emphasised and put into practice during college.
- Processing, requesting & following up with payments and invoices
- Gained experience in a remote role and in a number of complex systems

# July 2016 - Oct 2022

General manager at Satori BJJ

- All Reception duties- managing calendars & bookings
- Construction & Maintenance of www.satoribjj.com
- Marketing of Satori BJJ, Lead generation
- Teaching & planning classes. A skill emphasised and put into practice during college.
- Processing, requesting & following up with payments and invoices

# July 2016 - Oct 2022

Sub Only Events – Event Organiser

- Marketing Events via social media and mass emails
- Construction & Maintenance of <a href="https://www.jits.ie/">https://www.jits.ie/</a>
- Event organisation & coordination planning event dates & venues for a number of years in advance with long term growth strategies
- Customer Support & Dispute Resolution

## ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

- Training in Brazilian Jiu Jitsu
- Languages: Fluent English / Intermediate Russian & Latvian
- Enjoy attending hiring partner events whenever the opportunity presents itself
- Travel and video games are other interests of mine!